# MELISSA WARD

# UX/UI AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

#### CONTACT

mmacward99@gmail.com

wardmelissa.com

#### SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

CSS & HTML

Figma

Github

Graphic Design

CMS Management

### EDUCATION

Media, Arts, and Design

James Madison University 2018-2022

#### AWARDS

2022

Hashtag Sports Award Co-Nominee

#### PROFILE

Hi, my name is Melissa Ward, UX/UI and Graphic Designer from Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. Since May of 2022 I have worked as Web Seasonal Associate for the Philadelphia Eagles, where I worked with the incredible team of Eagles Entertainment. I am a creative, adaptable, and hard-working individual with a passion for design.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Web Associate**

Philadelphia Eagles

2022-2023

- Co-lead design on specialty campaigns for the Eagles app
- Collaborated efficiently with various internal and external departments and clients
- · Worked alongside editorial staff to create copy for digital platforms
- Created graphics for internal, as well as partner website pages and app experiences
- Updated CMS as needed to keep website up-to-date
- Further developed knowledge of Adobe Creative Suite through creating various website headers and graphics

## **Digital Intern**

MidAtlantic Employers' Association

2021-2022

- Collaborated with Managing Director to edit PowerPoint decks
- Utilized template to provide a more current look and feel to over 20 different PowerPoint decks
- · Maintained strong communication throughout remote internship
- Received positive feedback from multiple member companies, generating additional business

## **Assistant manager**

Jules Thin Crust

2015-2021

- · Create and manage employee schedules,
- accommodating individual requests and requirements
- Ensured employees complied with company policies
- and procedures
- Manage all team members on shift, including cooks,
- food runners, servers, and hosts
- Respond quickly and efficiently to customer complaints